<resources>
    <string name="app_name">News_RecyclerView</string>

    <string name="heading1">Prioritise regional languages in court activities, says Law Minister Rijiju</string>
    <string name="heading2">Amarinder Singh, Sunil Jakhar made BJP national executive members</string>
    <string name="heading3">Doha-bound carrier suffers technical snag</string>
    <string name="heading4">Kerala High Court upholds anticipatory bail granted to Congress MLA Eldhose Kunnappilly in rape case</string>
    <string name="heading5">SC sets aside Kerala HC order granting pre-arrest bail to 4 in ISRO espionage case</string>
    <string name="heading6"> We don’t need to be told what to do on democracy: India’s Permanent Representative to the UN Amb Kamboj</string>
    <string name="heading7">Srinagar to Dholavira to Puri: G20 logo illuminates 100 monuments</string>
    <string name="heading8">G20 presidency begins: India says it will be the voice of Global South</string>
    <string name="heading9">As G20 president, PM Modi will be setting world agenda: Amitabh Kant</string>
    <string name="heading10">Work on new Parliament to finish by end of December, say officials</string>
    <string name="heading11">India assumes monthly presidency of UNSC</string>
    <string name="heading12">Centre defends redrawing J and K seats, tells Supreme Court 2019 law empowers it</string>
    <string name="heading13">German Foreign Minister Annalena Baerbock to begin 2-day visit on Dec 5</string>
    <string name="heading14">Mainpuri bypoll: EC tells SSP to relieve 6 cops from duty, asks him why deployment order not followed</string>
    <string name="heading15">Govt plans to introduce 16 new bills in upcoming Winter session of Parliament</string>
    <string name="desc1">Union Law and Justice Minister Kiren Rijiju on Friday batted for the use of regional languages in the curricular activities of the courts in the country and said he was opposed to “imposition” of one language.
        Rijiju also said easy access to justice is the “call of the time.” In his address at the 12th Convocation of the Tamil Nadu Dr Ambedkar Law University (TNDALU), he also praised the Tamil language.
        “As you all know, our Prime Minister (Narendra Modi) has a commitment to take the country forward along with our culture and our language. I also have been emphasising on this–that the Indian courts and the Indian legal system must have regional languages in the curricular activities.” “I have already spoken to the Chief Justice of
India, senior judges of the Supreme Court and all the Chief Justices of the High Courts, that in the future we must give priority to the regional languages,” he said.</string>

    <string name="desc2">The first meeting of the Congress steering committee constituted by party chief Mallikarjun Kharge began here on Sunday with the party top brass holding deliberations on the schedule and venue for its plenary session besides discussing key organisational matters.

Congress president Mallikarjun Kharge, former party chief Sonia Gandhi, Rajasthan Chief Minister Ashok Gehlot, his Chhattisgarh counterpart Bhupesh Baghel, senior leaders P Chidambaram, Anand Sharma, Meira Kumar and Ambika Soni were among those who attended the meeting.

Rahul Gandhi did not attend the meeting due to the Bharat Jodo Yatra which is set to enter Rajasthan on Sunday evening.</string>

    <string name="desc3">As India celebrated the Navy Day to mark the achievements in ‘Operation Trident’ during the 1971 Indo-Pak War, Prime Minister Narendra Modi and Defence Minister Rajnath Singh led the nation in sending out greetings.

“Best wishes on Navy Day to all navy personnel and their families. We in India are proud of our rich maritime history,” Modi said in a tweet.</string>

</resources>